David Flynn-Coutts

 • London, England, United Kingdom
 ■ d.coutts@gmail.com
 □ 07793516425
 ■ in/davidflynncoutts

SUMMARY

Senior Product Manager with 6 years of experience in health tech and telecommunications. I have a track record of driving revenue growth, streamlining operations and building products that people like to use. Seeking Senior Product Manager roles in London with a hybrid or flexible work model. I have the right to work in the UK and will not need visa sponsorship now or in the future.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Product Manager

August 2021 - Present, London

Consultant Connect Consultant Connect is a telemedicine SaaS platform. Primary Care (GP's) and Secondary Care (Specialists/Consultants) use the platform to talk about patients, helping patients to get the right care early, and keeping patients out of hospitals.

- · Delivered integration projects, including Scotland-wide digital dermatology and England-wide eReferrals (eRS), retaining £2M in at-risk contracts and driving 20% revenue growth through improved clinical workflows.
- · Managed the continuous improvement of our app and web platforms. These are used by clinicians across the UK, Myanmar and Lebanon to support over 33 million patients.

Product Manager

Vodafone New Zealand

January 2020 - August 2021, Auckland, New Zealand

Vodafone provides mobile, broadband, and pay TV solutions to consumer and enterprise customers.

- · Led a project that fixed broken billing in low-margin broadband products, recovering \$700k in revenue at a cost of \$12k in staffing, a 58x ROI.
- · Launched the Business Wireless Broadband product, securing 1,000 connections in the first month and achieving a monthly growth rate of 25% over the following six months.
- · Partnered with UX/CX, development, and marketing teams to deliver products that align with product strategy and business objectives.

Product & Propositions Manager

January 2018 - December 2019, Auckland, New Zealand

Skinny does award winning prepay mobile and broadband at great prices across NZ.

- · Created and rolled out targeted promotional campaigns including 'Free Data Weekends' that drove a 25% improvement in user spend and a 10% reduction in churn over Q4 2018.
- · Directed the redevelopment of the company's help-site, improving page views by 130% month-on-month and reducing load times by 60%, enhancing both customer experience and operational efficiency.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

University of Auckland · Auckland, New Zealand · 2018

SKILLS

LEADERSHIP & STRATEGY

- · Managed cross-functional teams of 7–10 professionals, driving project success through strategic prioritization and clear communication.
- · Experienced in applying prioritization frameworks to maximize product impact and align cross-functional teams.
- · Successfully led NHS Scotland's digital dermatology rollout—delivered on time, within budget, and under high-pressure conditions.

TECHNICAL SKILLS & TOOLS

- · Product & Project Management: Linear, JIRA, Trello, Zendesk, Confluence
- · Design & Prototyping: Figma
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot} \, \textbf{Collaboration:} \, \textbf{Slack, Google Workspace} \\$
- · Analytics & Monitoring: Mixpanel, Sentry, AWS CloudWatch, Notion
- · Methodologies: Agile (Scrum), Lean Product Development, User-Centered Design, Data-Driven Decision Making